getmytrip.com 2014-07-03

# GetMyTrip Privacy and Policy – Travels websites, India Travel Portals

|   
---  

|  PRIVACY POLICY OF GetMyTrip   
---  
|   
---  
**What information do we collect?**  
  
We collect information from you when you register on our site or place an order.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.  
  
**What do we use your information for?**  
  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * **To personalize your experience**

(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

  * **To improve customer service**

(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

  * **To process transactions**

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

  * **To send periodic emails**

The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.

**How do we protect your information?**  
  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

**Do we use cookies?**  
We do not use cookies.   
**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.   
**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.   
**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.   
**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy.   
**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

GetMyTrip.com  
**EDU POINT SOLUTION**  
No. S-2, Venkateshwara Castle,  
No. 30, Palat Sankaran Road,  
Mahalingapuram,   
Chennai - 600034.  
Contact Number :+91 - 44-30638000,  
Call Center No : +91 - 44-30604444.

Thanking you for using GetMyTrip!!!   

|   
---  
  
|   
---  
  
Copyright © 2014 - www.GetMyTrip.com All Rights Reserved.
